<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="80"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[Company Pro le






         2020]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[03 About Us

                                                                                                                                                                                                                           FOR A
                                                                                                                                       04 Company Statement                                                                BETTER DAY
                                                                                                                                                                                                                           @ WORK

                                                                                                                                       05 Mission, Vision, Core Values



                                                                                                                                       06 Business Network


                                                                                                                                       07 Showroom



                                                                                                                                       29 Our Product Range



                                                                                                                                       30 O ce & Lounge Furniture



                                                                                                                                       37 Contract  ooring



                                                                                                                                       43 Partition Walls



                                                                                                                                       48 Our Customer Services



                                                                                                                                       54 Projects We Are Proud Of                                                                     INDEX


                                                                                                                                       77 References

            Delight presents a wide range of

            products with clean lines and great

            functionality for your o ce space.]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[03 About Us

                                                                                                    FOR A
                04 Company Statement                                                                BETTER DAY
                                                                                                    @ WORK

                05 Mission, Vision, Core Values



                06 Business Network


                07 Showroom



                29 Our Product Range



                30 O ce & Lounge Furniture



                37 Contract  ooring



                43 Partition Walls



                48 Our Customer Services



                54 Projects We Are Proud Of                                                                     INDEX


                77 References

 Delight presents a wide range of

 products with clean lines and great

 functionality for your o ce space.]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[About Us                                                                Company Statement






                                                                                                                                Delight leads the way in creating great experiences by o ering a range of creative
                                                        We are the largest regional company specialized in                      solutions, architecture, furniture and technology products and services designed to help
                                                        developing complete workspace business                                  people reach their full potential.
                                                        solutions and interior design, project
                                                        management,  t-out works and o ce furniture supply                      Our comprehensive portfolio is anchored by three core brands: Steelcase, Interface, and
                                                        in the Adriatic region.                                                 Deko. Together with our partners, we design o ce spaces to help people work, learn and
                                                                                                                                heal. For over 20 years, Delight has helped to create inspirational & agile workplaces for the
                                                        In scope:                                                               world’s leading organizations, across all industries.


                                                         • Corporate O ce Solutions

                                                         • Since founding, Delight has continuously developed                   RESULTS
                                                        its range of services and partner relationships, becom-
                                                        ing the  rst fully-integrated o ce design & build
                                                        company in the Adriatic region.                                         Delight is a leading specialist in o ce and  workspace space design,
                                                                                                                                project management,  t-out, M&E works, refurbishment and o ce

                                                         • Delight regionally holds the authorized dealership                   furniture supply in ex YU region, covering market of over  20M people.
                                                        network of well-known Steelcase, a global leader in the
                                                        o ce furniture industry, Interface worldwide leader in                  20+ years
                                                        modular  ooring, and DEKO for partition walls systems.                  of innovating cosporate o ce solutions
                                                                                                                                100+ employees
                                                         • During  years of activity, Delight has delivered profes-             highly specialized and creative
                                                        sional services and adequate products to more than                      2500+ clients
                                                        3,000 companies that needed to create or transform
                                                        their workspaces.                                                       in di erent industries
                                                                                                                                15000+ projects
                                                                                                                                Succsesfully completed




                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          04]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[About Us  Company Statement






         Delight leads the way in creating great experiences by o ering a range of creative
 We are the largest regional company specialized in   solutions, architecture, furniture and technology products and services designed to help
 developing complete workspace business   people reach their full potential.
 solutions and interior design, project
 management,  t-out works and o ce furniture supply   Our comprehensive portfolio is anchored by three core brands: Steelcase, Interface, and
 in the Adriatic region.  Deko. Together with our partners, we design o ce spaces to help people work, learn and
         heal. For over 20 years, Delight has helped to create inspirational & agile workplaces for the
 In scope:   world’s leading organizations, across all industries.


  • Corporate O ce Solutions

  • Since founding, Delight has continuously developed   RESULTS
 its range of services and partner relationships, becom-
 ing the  rst fully-integrated o ce design & build
 company in the Adriatic region.  Delight is a leading specialist in o ce and  workspace space design,
         project management,  t-out, M&E works, refurbishment and o ce

  • Delight regionally holds the authorized dealership   furniture supply in ex YU region, covering market of over  20M people.
 network of well-known Steelcase, a global leader in the
 o ce furniture industry, Interface worldwide leader in   20+ years
 modular  ooring, and DEKO for partition walls systems.  of innovating cosporate o ce solutions
         100+ employees
  • During  years of activity, Delight has delivered profes-  highly specialized and creative
 sional services and adequate products to more than   2500+ clients
 3,000 companies that needed to create or transform
 their workspaces.  in di erent industries
         15000+ projects
         Succsesfully completed




                                                                                                                   04]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[Business


                          MISSION



                          Our mission is to create o ce spaces that foster collaboration, attract talents and              Network
                          engage workers to reach their full potential.
                          We implement high quality solutions that enhance the wellbeing of the employees and
                          support the brand awareness of our customers.







                          VISION



                          Our vision is to maintain the leading regional market position and shape the future
                          workspaces by implementing high quality sustainable products and solutions that will
                          integrate the newest and future technologies.








                           CORE VALUES



                           •  Customer Commitment and Support
                           •  Creativity
                           •  Quality
                           •  Integrity
                           •  E ciency
                           •  Teamwork                                                                                                                        52
                           •  Out of the box thinking

                                                                                                                              +386 8 20 54 007      +385 1 462 30 63      +381 11 414 9 200      +382 67 254 054         +389 2 323 01 89



    05                                                                                                                                                                            13]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[Business


 MISSION



 Our mission is to create o ce spaces that foster collaboration, attract talents and   Network
 engage workers to reach their full potential.
 We implement high quality solutions that enhance the wellbeing of the employees and
 support the brand awareness of our customers.







 VISION



 Our vision is to maintain the leading regional market position and shape the future
 workspaces by implementing high quality sustainable products and solutions that will
 integrate the newest and future technologies.








 CORE VALUES



 •  Customer Commitment and Support
 •  Creativity
 •  Quality
 •  Integrity
 •  E ciency
 •  Teamwork                           52
 •  Out of the box thinking

       +386 8 20 54 007      +385 1 462 30 63      +381 11 414 9 200     +382 67 254 054          +389 2 323 01 89



 05                                                        13]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[SHOWROOM]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[SHOWROOM]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[Belgrade



    09]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[Belgrade



 09]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[FOR A
                                                                                        BETTER DAY
                                                                                        @ WORK]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[FOR A
 BETTER DAY
 @ WORK]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[Skopje



                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          14]]></page><page Index="15"><![CDATA[Skopje



                                                                                                                   14]]></page><page Index="16"><![CDATA[FOR A
                                                                                                 BETTER DAY
                                                                                                 @ WORK]]></page><page Index="17"><![CDATA[FOR A
 BETTER DAY
 @ WORK]]></page><page Index="18"><![CDATA[Zagreb




































































    17]]></page><page Index="19"><![CDATA[Zagreb




































































 17]]></page><page Index="20"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="21"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="22"><![CDATA[Ljubljana



                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          22]]></page><page Index="23"><![CDATA[Ljubljana



                                                                                                                   22]]></page><page Index="24"><![CDATA[FOR A
                                                                                                                                      BETTER DAY
                                                                                                                                      @ WORK























































    23]]></page><page Index="25"><![CDATA[FOR A
               BETTER DAY
               @ WORK























































 23]]></page><page Index="26"><![CDATA[Podgorica



    25]]></page><page Index="27"><![CDATA[Podgorica



 25]]></page><page Index="28"><![CDATA[FOR A
                                                                                          BETTER DAY
                                                                                          @ WORK


















                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          26]]></page><page Index="29"><![CDATA[FOR A
 BETTER DAY
 @ WORK


















                                                                                                                   26]]></page><page Index="30"><![CDATA[Our product range                                                                                                     O ce & Lounge Furniture






           Quality matters. When you bring people together in spaces that best support their needs – where they                 O ce design is about more than creating an environment that provides all the furniture and equipment
           work, learn and heal – they will be more satis ed, productive and creative.
                                                                                                                                to support the various types of work tasks. Great o ce design goes beyond the physical, practical
                                                                                                                                concerns and takes into account the psychological and emotional well-being of the people who will be
                                                                                                                                using the space. It is well known that open space o ces are designed to support how people work,
                                                                                                                                creating an atmosphere where it’s easier to communicate with the rest of the team.

                                                                                                                                The workspace is changing all the time... Employees need space that is more  exible and that encourages
                                                                                                                                their productivity. The inevitable part of every modern interior is a space for relaxing and for work in a less
            FURNITURE                          CONTRACT FLOORING                     PARTITION WALLS                            formal atmosphere. There are a lot of carefully picked o ce accessories that provide mobility,

            LOUNGE & VISITOR FURNITURE         PVC FLOORING                          SYSTEM PARTITIONS                          support communication and teamwork. The organization of the workspace became a
            OFFICE FURNITURE                   CARPET TILES                          GLASS PARTITIONS                           very important part of a modern o ce.
            PREMIUM OFFICE FURNITURE           LUXURY VINYL TILES                    MOVABLE PARTITIONS

            DESIGNED FURNITURE                 PREMIUM RUBBER FLOORING               DOORS AND GLAS FLOORING





            ACCESSORIES                                                              TECHNOLOGY
            OFFICE DECOR + RUGS                                                      COLLABORATION

            LIGHTNING                                                                OPTIMIZATION & ANALYTICS
            ORGANIZATIONAL & TECHNICAL TOOLS                                         ACOUSTIC SOLUTIONS
            INTERACTIVE BOARDS















                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          30]]></page><page Index="31"><![CDATA[Our product range  O ce & Lounge Furniture






 Quality matters. When you bring people together in spaces that best support their needs – where they   O ce design is about more than creating an environment that provides all the furniture and equipment
 work, learn and heal – they will be more satis ed, productive and creative.
         to support the various types of work tasks. Great o ce design goes beyond the physical, practical
         concerns and takes into account the psychological and emotional well-being of the people who will be
         using the space. It is well known that open space o ces are designed to support how people work,
         creating an atmosphere where it’s easier to communicate with the rest of the team.

         The workspace is changing all the time... Employees need space that is more  exible and that encourages
         their productivity. The inevitable part of every modern interior is a space for relaxing and for work in a less
 FURNITURE  CONTRACT FLOORING  PARTITION WALLS  formal atmosphere. There are a lot of carefully picked o ce accessories that provide mobility,

 LOUNGE & VISITOR FURNITURE  PVC FLOORING  SYSTEM PARTITIONS   support communication and teamwork. The organization of the workspace became a
 OFFICE FURNITURE  CARPET TILES  GLASS PARTITIONS  very important part of a modern o ce.
 PREMIUM OFFICE FURNITURE  LUXURY VINYL TILES  MOVABLE PARTITIONS

 DESIGNED FURNITURE  PREMIUM RUBBER FLOORING   DOORS AND GLAS FLOORING





 ACCESSORIES  TECHNOLOGY
 OFFICE DECOR + RUGS  COLLABORATION

 LIGHTNING  OPTIMIZATION & ANALYTICS
 ORGANIZATIONAL & TECHNICAL TOOLS  ACOUSTIC SOLUTIONS
 INTERACTIVE BOARDS















                                                                                                                   30]]></page><page Index="32"><![CDATA[32]]></page><page Index="33"><![CDATA[32]]></page><page Index="34"><![CDATA[Partner Steelcase

                                                                                                                                                                                                          Steelcase leads the way in
                                                                                                                                                                                                          creating great experiences
                                                                                                                                                                                                          by o ering a range of
         Their passion is understanding people  in the o ce. They achieve that by observing the way people work to                                                                                        architecture, furniture and
         understand the needs for change of the individuals, teams, and organizations.                                                                                                                    technology products and
                                                                                                                                                                                                          services designed to help
         The journey have started in 1912. in Michigan, and the  rst patent they have gotten was in 1914. for steel                                                                                       people reach their full
         trashcan. This led to a metal desk, and ever since then, they have been going in the way of innovative                                                                                           potential.
         products and services. Sustainability is in the core of everything they do.
                                                                                                                                                                                                          Their comprehensive
         Whatever you want to achieve, Steelcase can provide you with the environment and tools to do it better,                                                                                          portfolio is anchored by
         faster and more e ciently.                                                                                                                                                                       three core brands:
                                                                                                                                                                                                          Steelcase, Coalesse and
                                                                                                                                                                                                          Turnstone. Together with
                                                                                                                                                                                                          their partners, they design
                                                                                                                                                                                                          spaces to help people
                                                                                                                                                                                                          work, learn and heal.


                                                                                                                                                                                                          And because protecting
                                                                                                                                                                                                          the environment is in their
                                                                                                                                                                                                          DNA, they drive
                                                                                                                                                                                                          sustainable social,
                                                                                                                                                                                                          economic and
                                                                                                                                                                                                          environmental change
                                                                                                                                                                                                          through our decisions and
                                                                                                                                                                                                          actions. At Steelcase, they
                                                                                                                                                                                                          don’t just do what’s right,
                                                                                                                                                                                                          we do what’s best — for
                                                                                                                                                                                                          people and for the planet.








                                                                   07 06
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          34]]></page><page Index="35"><![CDATA[Partner Steelcase

                                                                                   Steelcase leads the way in
                                                                                   creating great experiences
                                                                                   by o ering a range of
 Their passion is understanding people  in the o ce. They achieve that by observing the way people work to   architecture, furniture and
 understand the needs for change of the individuals, teams, and organizations.     technology products and
                                                                                   services designed to help
 The journey have started in 1912. in Michigan, and the  rst patent they have gotten was in 1914. for steel   people reach their full
 trashcan. This led to a metal desk, and ever since then, they have been going in the way of innovative  potential.
 products and services. Sustainability is in the core of everything they do.
                                                                                   Their comprehensive
 Whatever you want to achieve, Steelcase can provide you with the environment and tools to do it better,   portfolio is anchored by
 faster and more e ciently.                                                        three core brands:
                                                                                   Steelcase, Coalesse and
                                                                                   Turnstone. Together with
                                                                                   their partners, they design
                                                                                   spaces to help people
                                                                                   work, learn and heal.


                                                                                   And because protecting
                                                                                   the environment is in their
                                                                                   DNA, they drive
                                                                                   sustainable social,
                                                                                   economic and
                                                                                   environmental change
                                                                                   through our decisions and
                                                                                   actions. At Steelcase, they
                                                                                   don’t just do what’s right,
                                                                                   we do what’s best — for
                                                                                   people and for the planet.








 07 06
                                                                                                                   34]]></page><page Index="36"><![CDATA[Steelcase Brands


                                                                                                                                                                             PolyVision CeramicSteel surfaces are used for whiteboards,
                                                                                                                                                                             chalkboards and an array of architectural applications.
                                                                                                                                                                             For over 60 years, PolyVision has produced durable
                                                                                                                                                                             and sustainable CeramicSteel surfaces that stand the test of time
                                                                                                                                                                             even in the most demanding environments.


                                                      Coalesse creates destinations that bring new life to work.
                                                      Led by intuition, backed by research, and driven by design
                                                      we help you bring new life to work.
                                                                                                                                                                             Orangebox is a designer and manufacturer of furniture for
                                                                                                                                                                             the changing workplace with a focus on “Smartworking”
                                                                                                                                                                             solutions – furniture that fosters collaboration while providing
                                                                                                                                                                             contemporary aesthetics, visual/acoustic privacy and
                                                                                                                                                                             commercial-grade performance.






                                                      From education to entrepreneurship to enterprise,
                                                      Turnstone makes cleverly simple furnishings for people                                                                 We design for young minds. With a century of experience,
                                                      who want to start something new.                                                                                       we’ve learned what makes pre-K-12 education di erent from

                                                                                                                                                                             any other environment (spoiler alert: quite a lot), and have
                                                                                                                                                                             made it our business to cater to those unique qualities.









                                                      Designtex is the leading company in the design and
                                                      manufacturing of applied materials for the built environment.

                                                      Environmental responsibility is fundamental to our business.                                                           AMQ specializes in supporting open plan design ideas with
                                                      Precision, is one of the  rst upholstery textiles in the                                                               height adjustable solutions, benching and seating for
                                                      industry to achieve gold level certi cation under the                                                                  collaborative environments.
                                                      Facts Sustainability Ecolabel..

    35                                                                                                                                                                                                                                    36]]></page><page Index="37"><![CDATA[Steelcase Brands


                                                      PolyVision CeramicSteel surfaces are used for whiteboards,
                                                      chalkboards and an array of architectural applications.
                                                      For over 60 years, PolyVision has produced durable
                                                      and sustainable CeramicSteel surfaces that stand the test of time
                                                      even in the most demanding environments.


 Coalesse creates destinations that bring new life to work.
 Led by intuition, backed by research, and driven by design
 we help you bring new life to work.
                                                      Orangebox is a designer and manufacturer of furniture for
                                                      the changing workplace with a focus on “Smartworking”
                                                      solutions – furniture that fosters collaboration while providing
                                                      contemporary aesthetics, visual/acoustic privacy and
                                                      commercial-grade performance.






 From education to entrepreneurship to enterprise,
 Turnstone makes cleverly simple furnishings for people  We design for young minds. With a century of experience,
 who want to start something new.                     we’ve learned what makes pre-K-12 education di erent from

                                                      any other environment (spoiler alert: quite a lot), and have
                                                      made it our business to cater to those unique qualities.









 Designtex is the leading company in the design and
 manufacturing of applied materials for the built environment.

 Environmental responsibility is fundamental to our business.   AMQ specializes in supporting open plan design ideas with
 Precision, is one of the  rst upholstery textiles in the   height adjustable solutions, benching and seating for
 industry to achieve gold level certi cation under the   collaborative environments.
 Facts Sustainability Ecolabel..

 35                                                                                                                36]]></page><page Index="38"><![CDATA[Contract Flooring






          As the design of o ce spaces becomes more advanced – taking into consideration the well-being and
          productivity of the people using them and the environmental impact of the materials involved –
          we’ve partnered with a leading company that produces modular  ooring and support services
          to meet any brief.

          For the majority of projects, acoustic and ergonomic comfort can be achieved with the speci c carpet tiles.
          Chairs being moved or footsteps on a  oor are examples of impact sound. A good acoustic environment is
          the result of many factors, but to e ectively control noise from footsteps and other impacts, no other
           ooring solution is more e ective than modular carpet tiles.









































    37]]></page><page Index="39"><![CDATA[Contract Flooring






 As the design of o ce spaces becomes more advanced – taking into consideration the well-being and
 productivity of the people using them and the environmental impact of the materials involved –
 we’ve partnered with a leading company that produces modular  ooring and support services
 to meet any brief.

 For the majority of projects, acoustic and ergonomic comfort can be achieved with the speci c carpet tiles.
 Chairs being moved or footsteps on a  oor are examples of impact sound. A good acoustic environment is
 the result of many factors, but to e ectively control noise from footsteps and other impacts, no other
  ooring solution is more e ective than modular carpet tiles.









































 37]]></page><page Index="40"><![CDATA[39                                                                                                                                                                                                                                    40]]></page><page Index="41"><![CDATA[39                                                                                                                40]]></page><page Index="42"><![CDATA[Partner Interface



                                                                                                                                                                             No negative impact?



          After discovering carpet tile in Europe in the early 1970s, Ray C. Anderson recognised its future in modern                                                        Mission possible.
          o ces. Open plan o ce systems were emerging, bringing with them the need to easily access  at wire
          and Walker duct systems – state of the art infrastructure at the time. In 1973, Ray founded Interface in
          LaGrange, GA, bringing the concept of free lay carpet tile to America and beginning a revolution in com-
          mercial  oorcovering.


          Interface entered the 21st century and delivered one innovation after another. In 2000 they rede ned
          modular carpet with the introduction of Entropy® and the emerging i2® category of products. That same
          year they o ered the  rst commercial carpet collection to use recycled nylon in the face  ber and a 100%
          recycled content vinyl backing layer.

          Over their 25-year sustainability journey, they’ve evolved their thinking and approach. Originally, they
          focused only on reducing environmental impacts, but that evolved to include social impacts and new
          business models.



                                                                                                                                 In 1994, inspired by their customers,
                                                                                                                                 they set out to eliminate their negative
                                                                                                                                 impact on the environment. Today,
                                                                                                                                 Interface is proud to have delivered on
                                                                                                                                 Mission Zero® commitment, in part by
                                                                                                                                 becoming the  rst global  ooring
                                                                                                                                 manufacturer to sell all products as
                                                                                                                                 carbon neutral across their full life
                                                                                                                                 cycle.


                                                                                                                                 Along the way, they’ve learned a thing
                                                                                                                                 or two about business models, solving
                                                     09
                                                                                                                                 material challenges and
                                                                                                                                 shooting for the moon.



    41]]></page><page Index="43"><![CDATA[Partner Interface



                                                      No negative impact?



 After discovering carpet tile in Europe in the early 1970s, Ray C. Anderson recognised its future in modern   Mission possible.
 o ces. Open plan o ce systems were emerging, bringing with them the need to easily access  at wire
 and Walker duct systems – state of the art infrastructure at the time. In 1973, Ray founded Interface in
 LaGrange, GA, bringing the concept of free lay carpet tile to America and beginning a revolution in com-
 mercial  oorcovering.


 Interface entered the 21st century and delivered one innovation after another. In 2000 they rede ned
 modular carpet with the introduction of Entropy® and the emerging i2® category of products. That same
 year they o ered the  rst commercial carpet collection to use recycled nylon in the face  ber and a 100%
 recycled content vinyl backing layer.

 Over their 25-year sustainability journey, they’ve evolved their thinking and approach. Originally, they
 focused only on reducing environmental impacts, but that evolved to include social impacts and new
 business models.



          In 1994, inspired by their customers,
          they set out to eliminate their negative
          impact on the environment. Today,
          Interface is proud to have delivered on
          Mission Zero® commitment, in part by
          becoming the  rst global  ooring
          manufacturer to sell all products as
          carbon neutral across their full life
          cycle.


          Along the way, they’ve learned a thing
          or two about business models, solving
 09
          material challenges and
          shooting for the moon.



 41]]></page><page Index="44"><![CDATA[Partition Walls                                                                                                     Partner Deko








             For  exibility and functionality. Solutions with                                                                    Since 1970, DEKO has developed
              exible partitions are very valuable for                                                                            products for interior  tting out of
             contemporary spaces.                                                                                                buildings, and today they are a
                                                                                                                                 well-consolidated company with an
             It is of great importance that the construction                                                                     internationally recognised brand.
             and deconstruction are easy and quick, and
             adaptable to all spaces. The main idea is the                                                                       DEKO is one of Scandinavia's leading
             maximum usage of the space available.                                                                               suppliers of partitioning solutions and
                                                                                                                                 one of Denmark's largest carpentry
             Daylight has an important role in making an                                                                         businesses specialising in the design of
             ambient appeal, whether it is an o ce space                                                                         o ce, business and institution
             or recreative space.                                                                                                buildings.


             Small o ces with dimmed light are replaced                                                                          DEKO are global leaders in the design,
             with spacious, comfortable spaces with optimal                                                                      manufacture and supply of sustainable
             usage of daylight. And it is proven that there is a                                                                 system partitions.
             positive impact on employee performance,
             content, and communication.                                                                                         The product range has
                                                                                                                                 well-established markets in Europe,
                                                                                                                                 Africa and Asia and comprises
                                                                                                                                 beautifully designed and engineered
                                                                                                                                 components, giving the architect and
                                                                                                                                 designer the capacity to achieve
                                                                                                                                 ambitious and thought.












    43                                                                                                                                                                                                                                   44]]></page><page Index="45"><![CDATA[Partition Walls  Partner Deko








 For  exibility and functionality. Solutions with   Since 1970, DEKO has developed
  exible partitions are very valuable for   products for interior  tting out of
 contemporary spaces.  buildings, and today they are a
          well-consolidated company with an
 It is of great importance that the construction   internationally recognised brand.
 and deconstruction are easy and quick, and
 adaptable to all spaces. The main idea is the   DEKO is one of Scandinavia's leading
 maximum usage of the space available.  suppliers of partitioning solutions and
          one of Denmark's largest carpentry
 Daylight has an important role in making an   businesses specialising in the design of
 ambient appeal, whether it is an o ce space   o ce, business and institution
 or recreative space.   buildings.


 Small o ces with dimmed light are replaced   DEKO are global leaders in the design,
 with spacious, comfortable spaces with optimal   manufacture and supply of sustainable
 usage of daylight. And it is proven that there is a   system partitions.
 positive impact on employee performance,
 content, and communication.  The product range has
          well-established markets in Europe,
          Africa and Asia and comprises
          beautifully designed and engineered
          components, giving the architect and
          designer the capacity to achieve
          ambitious and thought.












 43                                                                                                               44]]></page><page Index="46"><![CDATA[46]]></page><page Index="47"><![CDATA[46]]></page><page Index="48"><![CDATA[The only partitioning
         company to hold two ETA approvals
         for partition systems in Europe, and
         the  rst company to receive CE
         labelling for its glazed
         partition systems.

         DEKO’s intensive product develop-
         ment continues, pushing the
         boundaries to provide solutions
         which are sensitive to the environ-
         ment, safety and regulation
         compliant, whilst breaking the
         mould in terms of the application
         of glass in interior architecture.

         Being a contractor in Denmark as
         well as an international supplier
         makes DEKO unique.









         Continuous product development bene ts from our own hands-on experience of DEKO products in a                         Our
         variety of construction applications as well as embracing the wide ranging, international trends provid-
         ed by our extensive family of distributors.
                                                                                                                               Customer
         DEKO have recently coupled considerable investment and new technology to design and test
         an advanced range of  re and acoustic glazed partitions, fully embracing the latest glass
                                                                                                                               Services
         technology to create exciting possibilities for construction application.



    47                                                                                                                                                                                                                                   48]]></page><page Index="49"><![CDATA[The only partitioning
 company to hold two ETA approvals
 for partition systems in Europe, and
 the  rst company to receive CE
 labelling for its glazed
 partition systems.

 DEKO’s intensive product develop-
 ment continues, pushing the
 boundaries to provide solutions
 which are sensitive to the environ-
 ment, safety and regulation
 compliant, whilst breaking the
 mould in terms of the application
 of glass in interior architecture.

 Being a contractor in Denmark as
 well as an international supplier
 makes DEKO unique.









 Continuous product development bene ts from our own hands-on experience of DEKO products in a   Our
 variety of construction applications as well as embracing the wide ranging, international trends provid-
 ed by our extensive family of distributors.
        Customer
 DEKO have recently coupled considerable investment and new technology to design and test
 an advanced range of  re and acoustic glazed partitions, fully embracing the latest glass
        Services
 technology to create exciting possibilities for construction application.



 47                                                                                                               48]]></page><page Index="50"><![CDATA[Interior works                                                                                   Replacement furniture





                                            Regardless of whether you are upgrading to bigger space, remodeling into                                             From the moment you decide to equip your space and order your furniture,
                                    a surrounding with speci c  needs or you are adjusting to the new way of working,                                              in the period following the delivery we can provide replacement furniture.
                we can provide you with the necessary support to create the space you desire – from idea to realization.]]></page><page Index="51"><![CDATA[Interior works                                            Replacement furniture





 Regardless of whether you are upgrading to bigger space, remodeling into   From the moment you decide to equip your space and order your furniture,
 a surrounding with speci c  needs or you are adjusting to the new way of working,   in the period following the delivery we can provide replacement furniture.
 we can provide you with the necessary support to create the space you desire – from idea to realization.]]></page><page Index="52"><![CDATA[Free furniture testing                                                                                                                                   Moving





                   In order to feel all the advantages of our chairs, above all the functionality and quality of production,                                     Organization and the transition from one area to another can be a headache.
                           we made it possible to test free all models without any obligation for a period of seven days.                Therefore leave this work to our experienced team and you will be in the new area as soon as possible.]]></page><page Index="53"><![CDATA[Free furniture testing                                                                          Moving





 In order to feel all the advantages of our chairs, above all the functionality and quality of production,   Organization and the transition from one area to another can be a headache.
 we made it possible to test free all models without any obligation for a period of seven days.  Therefore leave this work to our experienced team and you will be in the new area as soon as possible.]]></page><page Index="54"><![CDATA[Projects



                                                                    After Sales Support                                        We Are





                    The satisfaction of our customers is our main reference. This is reason enough to stay in touch with you,
       to provide you with any form of support, consultation and recommendations for regular maintenance of our products.      Proud Of


                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          54]]></page><page Index="55"><![CDATA[Projects



 After Sales Support  We Are





 The satisfaction of our customers is our main reference. This is reason enough to stay in touch with you,
 to provide you with any form of support, consultation and recommendations for regular maintenance of our products.  Proud Of


                                                                                                                   54]]></page><page Index="56"><![CDATA[Huawei
                                                                                                                                                                                                          Industry: Information Technology
                                                                                                                                                                                                          Location: Belgrade, Serbia
                                                                                                                                                                                                          Size: 1000 m2






























    55]]></page><page Index="57"><![CDATA[Huawei
                                                                                   Industry: Information Technology
                                                                                   Location: Belgrade, Serbia
                                                                                   Size: 1000 m2






























 55]]></page><page Index="58"><![CDATA[Digitec Galaxus
           Industry: Consumer Goods
           Location: Belgrade, Serbia
           Size: 500m²






























                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          58]]></page><page Index="59"><![CDATA[Digitec Galaxus
 Industry: Consumer Goods
 Location: Belgrade, Serbia
 Size: 500m²






























                                                                                                                   58]]></page><page Index="60"><![CDATA[Infosys Limited
                                                                                                                                                                                                          Industry: Information Technology
                                                                                                                                                                                                          Location: Karlovac, Croatia
































    59]]></page><page Index="61"><![CDATA[Infosys Limited
                                                                                   Industry: Information Technology
                                                                                   Location: Karlovac, Croatia
































 59]]></page><page Index="62"><![CDATA[SMSGlobal
           Industry: Information Technology
           Location: Zagreb, Croatia
           Size: 350m2






























                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          62]]></page><page Index="63"><![CDATA[SMSGlobal
 Industry: Information Technology
 Location: Zagreb, Croatia
 Size: 350m2






























                                                                                                                   62]]></page><page Index="64"><![CDATA[Hocoma
                                                                                                                                                                                                               Industry: Medical
                                                                                                                                                                                                               Location: Ljubljana, Slovenia
                                                                                                                                                                                                               Size: 600m2






























    63]]></page><page Index="65"><![CDATA[Hocoma
                                                                                        Industry: Medical
                                                                                        Location: Ljubljana, Slovenia
                                                                                        Size: 600m2






























 63]]></page><page Index="66"><![CDATA[PWC
           Industry: Professional services
           Location: Ljubljana, Slovenia
           Size: 1000m2






























                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          66]]></page><page Index="67"><![CDATA[PWC
 Industry: Professional services
 Location: Ljubljana, Slovenia
 Size: 1000m2






























                                                                                                                   66]]></page><page Index="68"><![CDATA[Allocate Software
                                                                                                                                                                                                          Industry: Information Technology
                                                                                                                                                                                                          Location: Skopje, Macedonia
































    67]]></page><page Index="69"><![CDATA[Allocate Software
                                                                                   Industry: Information Technology
                                                                                   Location: Skopje, Macedonia
































 67]]></page><page Index="70"><![CDATA[Globeks
           Industry: Professional services
           Location: Skopje, Macedonia
           Size: 400m2






























                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          70]]></page><page Index="71"><![CDATA[Globeks
 Industry: Professional services
 Location: Skopje, Macedonia
 Size: 400m2






























                                                                                                                   70]]></page><page Index="72"><![CDATA[Hotel Melia
                                                                                                                                                                                                           Industry: Hotel & Resorts
                                                                                                                                                                                                           Location: Podgorica, Montenegro
































    71]]></page><page Index="73"><![CDATA[Hotel Melia
                                                                                    Industry: Hotel & Resorts
                                                                                    Location: Podgorica, Montenegro
































 71]]></page><page Index="74"><![CDATA[Philip Morris
           Industry: Tobacco company
           Location: Podgorica, Montenegro
           Size: 500m2






























                                                                                                                                                                                                                                         74]]></page><page Index="75"><![CDATA[Philip Morris
 Industry: Tobacco company
 Location: Podgorica, Montenegro
 Size: 500m2






























                                                                                                                  74]]></page><page Index="76"><![CDATA[FOR MORE OFFICE SOLUTIONS


                                                                                                                                                                                                                VISIT US AT

                                                                                                                                                                                                           delighto ce.com]]></page><page Index="77"><![CDATA[FOR MORE OFFICE SOLUTIONS


                                                                                         VISIT US AT

                                                                                    delighto ce.com]]></page><page Index="78"><![CDATA[References





























































                                                                                                                                                                                   ... and many other satis ed clients

    77]]></page><page Index="79"><![CDATA[References





























































                                                            ... and many other satis ed clients

 77]]></page><page Index="80"><![CDATA[FOR A





                                     BETTER DAY





                                     @ WORK]]></page></pages></Search>